(this.webpackJsonpquiz=this.webpackJsonpquiz||[]).push([[0],{10:function(e,t,r){},12:function(e,t,r){"use strict";r.r(t);var c=r(1),n=r.n(c),o=r(5),a=r.n(o),s=r(2),i=(r(10),r(3)),u=r.p+"static/media/intro.f85cdbd2.mp3",d=r.p+"static/media/correct.160572d7.mp3",l=r.p+"static/media/wrong.e9468218.mp3",m=r(0);var x=function(e){var t=e.data,r=e.setStop,n=e.questionNumber,o=e.setQuestionNumber,a=Object(c.useState)(null),x=Object(s.a)(a,2),b=x[0],h=x[1],j=Object(c.useState)(null),f=Object(s.a)(j,2),p=f[0],O=f[1],v=Object(c.useState)("answer"),w=Object(s.a)(v,2),N=w[0],q=w[1],S=Object(i.a)(u),g=Object(s.a)(S,1)[0],y=Object(i.a)(d),M=Object(s.a)(y,1)[0],$=Object(i.a)(l),I=Object(s.a)($,1)[0];Object(c.useEffect)((function(){g()}),[g]),Object(c.useEffect)((function(){h(t[n-1])}),[t,n]);var R=function(e,t){setTimeout((function(){t()}),e)};return Object(m.jsxs)("div",{className:"quiz",children:[Object(m.jsx)("div",{className:"question",children:null===b||void 0===b?void 0:b.question}),Object(m.jsx)("div",{className:"answers",children:null===b||void 0===b?void 0:b.answers.map((function(e){return Object(m.jsx)("div",{className:p===e?N:"answer",onClick:function(){return function(e){O(e),q("answer active"),R(3e3,(function(){return q(e.correct?"answer correct":"answer wrong")})),R(5e3,(function(){e.correct?(M(),R(1e3,(function(){o((function(e){return e+1})),O(null)}))):(I(),R(1e3,(function(){r(!0)})))}))}(e)},children:e.text},e.id)}))})]})};var b=function(e){var t=e.setStop,r=e.questionNumber,n=Object(c.useState)(30),o=Object(s.a)(n,2),a=o[0],i=o[1];return Object(c.useEffect)((function(){if(0===a)return t(!0);var e=setInterval((function(){i((function(e){return e-1}))}),1e3);return function(){return clearInterval(e)}}),[t,a]),Object(c.useEffect)((function(){i(30)}),[r]),a};var h=function(e){var t=e.setUsername,r=Object(c.useRef)();return Object(m.jsxs)("div",{className:"start",children:[Object(m.jsx)("input",{placeholder:"ENTER YOUR NAME HERE..",className:"startInput",ref:r}),Object(m.jsx)("button",{className:"startButton",onClick:function(){r.current.value&&t(r.current.value)},children:"START"})]})};var j=function(){var e=Object(c.useState)(null),t=Object(s.a)(e,2),r=t[0],n=t[1],o=Object(c.useState)(1),a=Object(s.a)(o,2),i=a[0],u=a[1],d=Object(c.useState)(!1),l=Object(s.a)(d,2),j=l[0],f=l[1],p=Object(c.useState)("$ 0"),O=Object(s.a)(p,2),v=O[0],w=O[1],N=Object(c.useMemo)((function(){return[{id:1,amount:"$ 100"},{id:2,amount:"$ 200"},{id:3,amount:"$ 300"},{id:4,amount:"$ 500"},{id:5,amount:"$ 1000"},{id:6,amount:"$ 2000"},{id:7,amount:"$ 4000"},{id:8,amount:"$ 8000"},{id:9,amount:"$ 16000"},{id:10,amount:"$ 32000"},{id:11,amount:"$ 64000"},{id:12,amount:"$ 125000"},{id:13,amount:"$ 250000"},{id:14,amount:"$ 500000"},{id:15,amount:"$ 1000000"}].reverse()}),[]);return Object(c.useEffect)((function(){i>1&&w(N.find((function(e){return e.id===i-1})).amount)}),[N,i]),Object(m.jsx)("div",{className:"app",children:r?Object(m.jsxs)(m.Fragment,{children:[Object(m.jsx)("div",{className:"main",children:j?Object(m.jsxs)("h1",{className:"endText",children:["You earned: ",v," "]}):Object(m.jsxs)(m.Fragment,{children:[Object(m.jsx)("div",{className:"top",children:Object(m.jsx)("div",{className:"timer",children:Object(m.jsx)(b,{setStop:f,questionNumber:i})})}),Object(m.jsx)("div",{className:"bottom",children:Object(m.jsx)(x,{data:[{id:1,question:"Who develop React.JS?",answers:[{text:"Apple",correct:!1},{text:"Google",correct:!1},{text:"Twitter",correct:!1},{text:"Facebook",correct:!0}]},{id:2,question:"What is React.JS?",answers:[{text:"Server-side Framework",correct:!1},{text:"User-interface framework",correct:!1},{text:"A Library for building interaction interfaces",correct:!0},{text:"None of the above",correct:!1}]},{id:3,question:"What is used in React.JS to increase performance?",answers:[{text:"Virtual DOM",correct:!0},{text:"Original DOM",correct:!1},{text:"Both",correct:!1},{text:"None of the above",correct:!1}]},{id:4,question:" React.JS in MVC is?",answers:[{text:"Model",correct:!1},{text:"Middleware",correct:!1},{text:"Method",correct:!1},{text:"Controller",correct:!0}]},{id:5,question:"Everything in React is ?",answers:[{text:"Component",correct:!0},{text:"Model",correct:!1},{text:"Method",correct:!1},{text:"Package",correct:!1}]},{id:6,question:"React component can return how many components ?",answers:[{text:"one",correct:!1},{text:"multiple",correct:!0},{text:"two",correct:!1},{text:"three",correct:!1}]},{id:7,question:"Name the function used to change the state of react component ?",answers:[{text:"this.setState",correct:!0},{text:"this.setChangeState",correct:!1},{text:"this.State{}",correct:!1},{text:"Both A and B",correct:!1}]},{id:8,question:"What are props into other components ?",answers:[{text:"Injected",correct:!1},{text:"Both A and D",correct:!1},{text:"None of the above",correct:!1},{text:"Method",correct:!0}]},{id:9,question:"What is state in React?",answers:[{text:" A permanent storage",correct:!1},{text:"Internal storage of the component",correct:!0},{text:"Both A and B",correct:!1},{text:" None of the above",correct:!1}]},{id:10,question:"What will happen if you render an input element with disabled = {false}?",answers:[{text:" It will be rendered as disabled",correct:!1},{text:" It will be rendered as enabled",correct:!0},{text:"It will not be rendered at all",correct:!1},{text:"Nothing will be happened",correct:!1}]},{id:11,question:"Default port where webpack-server will run ?",answers:[{text:"8080",correct:!0},{text:"3333",correct:!1},{text:"3030",correct:!1},{text:"6020",correct:!1}]},{id:12,question:"Which of the following below act as the input of a class-based component?",answers:[{text:"props",correct:!0},{text:" class",correct:!1},{text:"factory",correct:!1},{text:"render",correct:!1}]},{id:13,question:"What is the declarative way to render a dynamic list of components based on values in an array?",answers:[{text:"Using the reduce array method",correct:!1},{text:"Using the <Each /> component",correct:!1},{text:"With a for/while loop",correct:!1},{text:"Using the Array.map() method",correct:!0}]},{id:14,question:" React.JS in MVC is?",answers:[{text:"Model",correct:!1},{text:"Middleware",correct:!1},{text:"Method",correct:!1},{text:"Controller",correct:!0}]},{id:15,question:"At the highest level, React components have lifecycle events that fall into?",answers:[{text:"Destruction",correct:!1},{text:"State/Property Updates",correct:!1},{text:"Initialization",correct:!1},{text:"All of the above",correct:!0}]}],setStop:f,setQuestionNumber:u,questionNumber:i})})]})}),Object(m.jsx)("div",{className:"pyramid",children:Object(m.jsx)("ul",{className:"moneyList",children:N.map((function(e){return Object(m.jsxs)("li",{className:i===e.id?"moneyListItem active":"moneyListItem",children:[Object(m.jsx)("span",{className:"moneyListItemNumber",children:e.id}),Object(m.jsx)("span",{className:"moneyListItemAmount",children:e.amount})]},e.id)}))})})]}):Object(m.jsx)(h,{setUsername:n})})};a.a.render(Object(m.jsx)(n.a.StrictMode,{children:Object(m.jsx)(j,{})}),document.getElementById("root"))}},[[12,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.2b492645.chunk.js.map